hello once again you are very
welcome to our YouTube channel, in today's
video we will do Tarzan 2,
his beak in the middle of the plan which is the
solution of Max Bupa, Compliant Bank and Yes Bank,
last name unknown, please watch this video
till the end because in this video
I will give you half inch recording information
which will be very useful for you in your life
and those who want to join the film of health insurance,
this car is related to speed,
they
can also cut through us, Masha, secondly,
let's start the video, first of all we will
know what is the difference between these plans, what are the
things that make these plans different from each other, first of all
we will talk about the
middle option, in the Max initiative Compliant
Bank, you
get high coverage options ranging from Rs. 1 crore and
in SBI Arogya Upavas, you get
reviews and options ranging from Rs. 30 lakh, in
which you will get
free laugh injury news in the comment section for three levels
and post graduation  You have a cover for four districts
and SBI Arogya Plus Bandhi Preeti
Half Year Edition you have a cover for seven districts
you have a cover
for sending now let's talk about treatment cover,
before I start covering it I will tell you
All the things that mean news is there in the entire
Sameshwar and SBI Arogya Plus in this
only your 142 treatment is covered,
you are
covered in emergency home recharges, in Max Bupa Health
companies you have a cover of ₹3000 and
in SBI Aloo Kepler Space you have
ambulance charges covered up to ₹1500, if we
talk about your cover then in Help Complaint
Plans OPD you get animal back cover
charges from ₹2500 to ₹
7000 and in the same SBI Arogya Plan you have
your expenses
covered up to ₹
10000 in Help Champion Plan
you have no limit on this, if you add
plan ₹299 plus limit you will have 65 years
friends this is the difference we will
talk about in these  In Clans lights,
in cases you should subscribe to this treatment, you get
channel subscription, all of you
friends today you get it, if you do
not subscribe to the channel,
you get the benefit of hospital cash,
for ₹1000 cards, ₹4000 Patel Anil
duty, you also get exit option
available, which is
available to you from one hand to ₹10 in help companies, now we will talk about
no claim bonus, friends maths,
in Google Lens complaint helpline you get
worship goddess 20 percent of this
mins that in every sphere which
goes up to maximum hundred percent, bonus marks
never reduce in fufa, you have to accept it,
now we will talk about little benefits,
in help from pension you get
default benefits hundred percent of this
mins that you
cannot use on meeting the same person after the commencement of the examination in your policy
and winters and  You get the benefit,
now
you also get the facility of Jasmine Child Health Checkup, on such or read ball,
now let's talk about some benefits which
you do not get only Ajwain Arogya Plus name,
yes madam ji's benefit you get is
speed limit, then in this you have meeting
Tiger No, now I will talk
about the personality of these plans which
is almost the same in implants, the initial waiting period
prevents this, for specific diseases
you have to wait for 24 months in Max Bupa Health Compliance Family and in
SBI Arogya Plan you
also have to wait for one year for specific diseases
pre-existing, for this you have to
wait for 36 years in Help [ __ ] Pension Plan
and in SBI Arogya Plan
you have to wait for 48 months,
friends this is a little information
about the comparison of Max Bupa Health Compliance Plan and SBI Arogya Plan and
please tell me through comments if
you like this video  How did you like it? If you have any question
related to this video then
ask it in the comment and if
you find this video very useful then share
this video with your relatives on WhatsApp.
What will happen by this, it will help them
and you will get thanks.
Don't forget to subscribe to the channel and like the video so
that my motivation remains the same
and I bring such informative videos for you.
Press the bell icon so that
you get the updates of my latest videos. Thank you for watching
my video
[Music]